logic_test = [
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "How much is 3 x 1?",
        "answer": "3",
        "choices": [3, 9, 12]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How much is 3 x 2?",
        "answer": "6",
        "choices": [6, 15, 3]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How much is 3 x 3?",
        "answer": "9",
        "choices": [6, 9, 12]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "How much is 3 x 4?",
        "answer": "12",
        "choices": [3, 9, 12]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How much is 3 x 5?",
        "answer": "15",
        "choices": [3, 15, 12]
    }
]

tecnical_test = [
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "JSON stands for ",
        "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation",
        "choices": ["JavaScript Object Notation", "JavaScript Object Normalization", "JavaScript Object-Oriented Notation"]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": " JSON is a _____ for storing and transporting data.",
        "answer": "text format",
        "choices": ["xml format", "text format", "JavaScript"]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The JSON syntax is a subset of the _____ syntax.",
        "answer": "JavaScript",
        "choices": ["Ajax", "JavaScript", "Php"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In the JSON syntax, data is separated by _____.",
        "answer": "Commas",
        "choices": ["Commas", "Colons", "Hyper"]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": " JSON names (keys) require double quotes?",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": ["True", "False", "None"]
    }
]